JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 7
TOSHIKAZU HAZAMADA (SHOW OFF)
HAZAMADA
SHOW OFF
TIME TO MEETING: 9 MINUTES
NO CROSSING
EPISODE 8
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
FALLS IN LOVE, PART 1